export const Questions = [
  {
    prompt:
      "Q1. The Squid Game is a game in which you either die or win a huge amount of prize money. If you are being invited, would you join?",
    optionA: "Yes",
    optionB: "No",
    optionC: "Maybe",
    optionD: "I don't know",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    prompt:
      "Q2. Unfortunately, this is the compulsory recruitment of the first testing version of Squid Game. Therefore, if you are invited, you have to participate. You were drugged unconscious and brought to an unknown and closed game field joining 499 other experiment subjects waiting for the game to start. What would you first focus on?",
    optionA: "The environment",
    optionB: "The Guards with guns",
    optionC: "My own physical condition",
    optionD: "The other participants",
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    prompt:
      "Q3. It might be easier to win the games with a partner in this game of life and death. Which of the following four people would you pick to form an ally?",
    optionA: "The shivering little boy who does not really talk",
    optionB: "The small and skinny young girl with a bright smile",
    optionC: "The white-haired old scholar",
    optionD: "The middle-aged male body builder",
    answer: "D",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Q4. What would you do after becoming a team?",
    optionA: "Take initiative to communicate, we should help each other.",
    optionB: "Stay alert and do not talk too much.",
    optionC: "Pass orders",
    optionD: "Get food for everyone",
    answer: "D",
  },
  {
    prompt:
      "Q5. During lunch time, the bully was bulling an old participant. Would you step in and stop him?",
    optionA: "Yes",
    optionB: "No",
    optionC: "I don't know",
    optionD: "I will ignore",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    prompt:
      "Q6. When having a meal with your teammate, what would you wish to talk about?",
    optionA: "The reason why he or she was here.",
    optionB: "Predict what the next game will be.",
    optionC: "Rarely",
    optionD:
      "Analyze the strengths, weaknesses and personalities of the other opponents",
    answer: "D",
  },
  {
    prompt:
      "Q7. The game is about to start, the game will start from the lowest number to the largest number in order, and each person will go individually. There are only four more numbers left for you to choose from, which one will you pick?",
    optionA: "No. 1",
    optionB: "No. 10",
    optionC: "No. 50",
    optionD: "No. 500",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    prompt:
      "Q8. [ Level One - At Fault ] A family of four, the older son was killed in a car accident by a drunk driver. After the death of the son, the father left home with all their savings. The mother cried non-stop every day with the photo of the son and abused the daughter. Finally, the daughter killed the mother and then committed suicide. Who was most at fault in the story?",
    optionA: "The father",
    optionB: "The mother",
    optionC: "The daughter",
    optionD: "The driver",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    prompt:
      "Q9. [ Level Two - Footsteps ] Three of the four rooms below have a hidden killer in them. Based on the description of the door, which room is safe?",
    optionA: "a sturdy, atmospheric, opaque glass door",
    optionB: "a simple and clean beige bamboo door",
    optionC: "a worn out and rusty iron door",
    optionD: "a dark red door covered in carvings",
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    prompt:
      "Q10. [ Level Three - Fate ] You can only save the life of one of the following people, please make your decision.",
    optionA: "A boy who lost one of his legs from saving someone.",
    optionB: "A superstar with tons of fans.",
    optionC: "A woman of advanced maternal age who is pregnant with twins.",
    optionD: "An elderly scientist who had made a great contribution.",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    prompt:
      "Q11. The testing version of Squid Game is over. Fortunately, no one would really be eliminated in the testing version. Before leaving, you may ask the game creator a question and it would be answered. What would you ask?",
    optionA: "What is your real name?",
    optionB: "What is your real occupation?",
    optionC: "Why do you hold the Squid Game?",
    optionD: "After I leave, can I go back to  my life?",
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    prompt:
      "Q12. After experiencing the Squid Game in person, which are you more likely to do?",
    optionA: "Continue with my life and never speak of it again.",
    optionB: "Tell other and society after the experience.",
    optionC: "Try to get in contact with friends I have made in the game.",
    optionD: "Write novels and movies on related topics.",
    answer: "C",
  },
];
